He's coming.
Resurrection is a crime, mystery, horror film directed by Russell Mulcahy.
A jaded homicide detective has been put on the case of a ruthless killer in the city of Chicago, who leaves a
trail of horribly mutilated and dismembered corpses along with perversely ironic biblical quotes.
Det. John Prudhomme, played by Christopher Lambert.
Det. Andrew Hollinsworth, played by Leland Orser.
Sara Prudhomme, played by Barbara Tyson.
Paramedic, played by Jeff J.J. Authors.
Father Rousell, played by David Cronenberg.
Dolores Koontz, played by Jayne Eastwood.
Resurrection is a 1999 Police procedural horror film directed by Russell Mulcahy
and starring Christopher Lambert, Leland Orser and Robert Joy.
David Cronenberg appears in a cameo as a priest.
Lambert co-wrote the story for the film with Brad
Mirman, who also wrote the screenplay.
The film was theatrically released in most of Europe, Asia and
Australia, but went straight to DVD in the US.
It was also occasionally aired/streamed on television.
The film explores themes of chicago, illinois,
psychopath, detective, fbi, investigation.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.